His greatest challenge. Humanity's last hope.
Inferno is a mystery, thriller, action film directed by Ron Howard.
After waking up in a hospital with amnesia, professor Robert Langdon and a
doctor must race against time to foil a deadly global plot.
Robert Langdon, played by Tom Hanks.
Sienna Brooks, played by Felicity Jones.
Christoph Bouchard, played by Omar Sy.
Harry Sims, played by Irrfan Khan.
Elizabeth Sinskey, played by Sidse Babett Knudsen.
Bertrand Zobrist, played by Ben Foster.
Inferno is a 2016 American action mystery thriller film
directed by Ron Howard and written by David Koepp.
It is loosely based on the 2013 novel by Dan Brown.
The sequel to The Da Vinci Code (2006) and Angels & Demons (2009), it is
the third and final film in the Robert Langdon film series.
It stars Tom Hanks, reprising his role as Robert
Langdon, alongside Felicity Jones as Dr.
Sienna Brooks, Omar Sy, Sidse Babett Knudsen, Ben Foster, and Irrfan Khan.
Filming began on April 27, 2015, in Venice, Italy,
wrapping on July 21 of that year in Budapest.
Inferno premiered in Florence (one of its filming locations) on October 8, 2016, and was released in
the United States on October 28, ten years after the release of The Da Vinci Code.
The film received negative reviews from critics, and grossed $220
million against a $75 million production budget.
The film explores themes of amnesia, based on
novel or book, italy, europe, sequel.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.